<?xml version="1.0"?>
    <rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>whitep4nth3r.com | Build stuff, learn things, love what you do</title>
      <link>https://whitep4nth3r.com</link>
      <description>Live coding streamer, writer, speaker | whitep4nth3r.com | Build stuff, learn things, love what you do</description>
    </channel>
      
        <item>
        <title>5 tips for leading teams with an empathy-first approach</title>
        <description>As my time as an engineering team lead comes to an end and I move into DevRel in 2021 - I wrote about how I prioritise empathy in tech teams over everything - something that will continue to stay with me firmly as my career continues to evolve.</description>
        <author>whitep4nth3r</author>
        <link>https://whitep4nth3r.com/blog/5-tips-for-leading-teams-with-an-empathy-first-approach</link>
        <pubDate>2020-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</pubDate>
        <guid>634FrXaRshjsRxsgEcus4A</guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
        <title>My non-traditional journey into tech and DevRel</title>
        <description>We managed to catch Salma amidst her busy onboarding schedule to learn about what led her to developer relations and how she accidentally increased engagement in the [Contentful Community](https://www.contentful.com/slack/) by 200% on her first day at Contentful.</description>
        <author>whitep4nth3r</author>
        <link>https://whitep4nth3r.com/blog/my-non-traditional-journey-into-tech-and-devrel</link>
        <pubDate>2021-02-03T00:00:00.000Z</pubDate>
        <guid>1781UMYIdWzTDYtIEaG907</guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
        <title>How to build a lightweight microblogging site with Contentful, vanilla HTML, CSS and JavaScript</title>
        <description>Learn how to build a lightweight microblog with Contentful and vanilla HTML, CSS and JavaScript.</description>
        <author>whitep4nth3r</author>
        <link>https://whitep4nth3r.com/blog/how-to-build-a-lightweight-blog</link>
        <pubDate>2021-02-05T00:00:00.000Z</pubDate>
        <guid>2bwtZ3iGgOj5MZJSjUBlNg</guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
        <title>6 things I learned about streaming live coding in my first 6 weeks on Twitch</title>
        <description>I discovered live coding serendipitously on Twitch for the first time in mid June 2020. I was instantly hooked on the huge sense of community, the opportunities to learn, and the way in which the platform increases access to and engagement in science and technology content across the world.</description>
        <author>whitep4nth3r</author>
        <link>https://whitep4nth3r.com/blog/6-things-I-learned-about-streaming-live-coding-in-my-first-6-weeks-on-Twitch</link>
        <pubDate>2020-08-16T00:00:00.000Z</pubDate>
        <guid>38TaJGkfvY9RUqv9niBX7X</guid>
        </item>
        
    </rss>